{
    "subject": "resource/Roman_Catholic_Diocese_of_Udupi",
    "predicate": "ontology/territory",
    "object": "resource/Karnataka",
    "human_readable": "The Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi is located in Karnataka.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9381139874458313,
            "question": "Where is the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8753848075866699,
            "question": "Is the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi in India?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908099293708801,
            "question": "Can you name a diocese in Karnataka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7677310109138489,
            "question": "What state is home to the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7446616888046265,
            "question": "What kind of institution is the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7248281240463257,
            "question": "What are some of the services provided by the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987860798835754,
            "question": "What is the religious affiliation of the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6794405579566956,
            "question": "Does the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi have a specific geographical area it covers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6524047255516052,
            "question": "Are there any other dioceses in Karnataka besides the one mentioned?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5470588207244873,
            "question": "Are there any notable historical events associated with the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi is located in Karnataka.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5689_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other dioceses in Karnataka besides the one mentioned?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5689_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi have a specific geographical area it covers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5689_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the religious affiliation of the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5689_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5689_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention that the Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi is located in the city of Udupi, which is part of Karnataka. Therefore, the statement \"The Roman Catholic Diocese of Udupi is located in Karnataka\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}